God, keep my head above water. Don't let me drown
主   请将我的头靠在水面上   不要让我淹没
It gets harder. I'll meet you there at the altar
越来越困难了    我会在圣坛见到你
As I fall down to my knees
双膝跪拜
Don't let me drown drown drown
不要让我淹没 淹没 淹没
Don't let me, don't let me, don't let me drown
不要让我   不要让我   不要让我淹没
Don't let me drown drown drown
不要让我淹没 淹没 淹没
Keep my head above water, above water
请将我的头靠在水面上
And I can't see
在那恶劣的天气里
In the stormy weather
我无法将前路看清
I can't seem to keep it all together
似乎无法振作
And I can't swim the ocean like this forever
我无法永远潜游在这样的深海里
And I can't breath
我无法呼吸
God, keep my head above water
主   请将我的头靠在水面上
I lose my breath at the bottom
在那深底我无法呼吸
Come rescue me
快来将我拯救
I will be waiting
我始终在等着你
I'm too young to fall asleep
我还年轻不能就这样睡去
God, keep my head above water. Don't let me drown
主   请将我的头靠在水面上   不要让我淹没
It gets harder. I'll meet you there at the altar
越来越困难了    我会在圣坛见到你
As I fall down to my knees
双膝跪拜
Don't let me drown
不要让我淹没
Keep my head above water, above water.
请将我的头靠在水面上